<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Patrik on Tech</title>
    <link>http://patrikturi.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Patrik on Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Patrik Túri</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://patrikturi.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Work should not be hard</title>
      <link>http://patrikturi.com/posts/do-not-work-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patrikturi.com/posts/do-not-work-hard/</guid>
      <description>Work should not be hard and study should not be easy.
If work is really hard it means one of the following cases:
 You have no idea what you are doing You are trying to work and study at the same time You are overwhelmed  Either case you should stop. The first two means the results will be poor or even cause damage. The latter means you are risking burnout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StarCraft Applied to Software Development</title>
      <link>http://patrikturi.com/posts/starcraft-applied/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patrikturi.com/posts/starcraft-applied/</guid>
      <description>StarCraft 2 is one of the most difficult one versus one games. What can you learn from Starcraft and how does that help you become a better software developer?
Three Pillars of the Craft To be great at the game, one needs to master three areas:
 Game knowledge - Learn about SOLID principles and clean code. Know what you are doing. Execution of the strategy - There is no use of theory if you can not apply it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://patrikturi.com/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://patrikturi.com/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>I never had a blog, the idea didn&#39;t feel like something I would want to do. Now I see it is an important way to improve at writing and share my thoughts.
I&#39;m going to write primarily about software development. Other interests can kick in as well, or just truths I have observed in life.
The content is addressed to other developers and lighter topics to people who like logical thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>